The weather looks great today.
Man, I love peace and quiet.
What the hell?
I can hear my heart, and
どうしたけ言うの?
胸のボブが鳴る
始まりはあの時だった
君が眼の前に突然
現れたのは生まれる前から 決められてたんだね きっとそうだよ
願いや野望や空想が知らないレベルへ ドアを叩いて 羽ばたく花と未来をくれる
I can hear my heartbeat 止められないよ 天使が鳴らしてる 大好きの合図だよね
Can you hear my heartbeat どうしたって言うの 聞いたことがない 胸の弁が鳴る
これでもまだ 君は何にも知らないけれど
I can hear my heartbeat どうしたい
Why hello everyone My name is Ishiro Sugata
And this here is my assistant Pretty the second
Beginning around the year of 1280
And continuing for many decades the world saw a drastic surge in trade
The invention of the magnetic compass made this possible
However before the compass was widely in use
Mariners depended upon migrating birds and fish to determine ideal sailing routes
Explorers tracked these animals to discover the new world
There is an immeasurable level of potential in the magnetic compasses of animals
Go on Pretty use that internal compass of yours to show me the new world
Perhaps I would have been better off just cooking her for dinner instead
Damn why am I buried in panties again
I do not know
Perhaps they're similar to migratory birds
Oh come on
Wait a minute
Are you telling me all the panties from before came back
Yes
In fact I believe they circumnavigated the entire globe already
What?No way
It's possible they just wanted to see you master so they came back to visit
Crazy
You came all the way back here just to see me?
You guys
Tomo I am gonna
I better start running
You did it
What are all my panties doing here?
Why are they in your room?
You're such a pervert Tomo
I'm pervert
It's so...it's so horrible
Look Sohara look at all this lifeless fabric
They could have had bright futures ahead of them but no you had to ruin it
That's not it master
The effect of the card has simply worn off
Anyway
Every single one of them better go in the trash
I'm starting to get sick and tired of this foolishness
Sure you got it
Tomoki if I leave it to you you'll end up sniffing every last pair
I know
Hey Icarus
Yes miss it's right there
Score
What?They came back?
Yeah
When I woke up this morning the whole flock of panties came flying into my room
That's very interesting
You know the new world was discovered by tracking migratory birds
If we call the trajectory
Did I hear right?
Something about having a huge mound
Of panties lying around your house right now
Yeah
Let me see if I've got these sordid details straight
An innocent teenager has both used and unused panties flying around his bedroom
Like it's some perverse wonderland
Well they're not flying anymore
What about the pair Sahara was wearing?
Are they included in there as well Tomoki?
Well you are a guy so I guess I shouldn't act surprised
That's all I got no more questions from me
Tomo damn it you better promise you'll throw them out as soon as you get back home
Right
I'm on it
I don't think I can ever trust him again
Hey Tomoki
Have you gotten rid of those panties yet?
Hello
Tomo
Are you even listening?
Yeah
Taken care of
Good
Thank you
As if I'd ever throw them out
I'm a growing maturing teenager
I am needs
I'd be a fold apart ways with such a treasure trove
It's like my own personal holy grail
What the hell was that?
Oh lovely
You liar you didn't get rid of any of them
Sahara
Icarus here was kind enough to give me a special card of my own
She's on my side now
The panties will now
Explode
Let me break it down for you
If you so much as look at a pair of panties
They'll blow up in your face
Is that what just happened?
Exactly
I was hoping it'd make you less of a perverted freak show
Don't worry
It only affects panties within your vicinity
And it's just for one day
Judging by the size of that explosion
I bet you didn't throw out a single pair
You big fat liar
Icarus and I are gonna treat ourselves to a girl's day out
So even though I won't be here to witness it
Have fun moving around the house
Bye
Sahara wait
Feeling some regret
No
It's just there's um
A really big bug crawling on your wall
Ah
No way
Where
Where is it
Tomaki
Come on
Help me out
Where is it
Dumbass
You thought I wouldn't be able to see your panties under the windowsill
But you always get dressed with your window open
All of that peeping ate off
You jerk
You such a perv
I hate you
I hope you've been alive today
Okay
Let's get a move on Icarus
One moment
Master is not
Don't worry about him
He's on his own today
I gotta be careful
If I see any panties today
They'll turn into bombs
And blow my ass to smithereens
Dear you Sahara
I'm becoming a man
So of course I wanna fondle them and smell them and wear them
Anyway I gotta find a way out of here ASAP
I forgot I hung all of them up yesterday
This is bad
I'm gonna die if this keeps up
I gotta find a way out of here
And fast
Wait
If I don't look at them they can't explode right
Oh man this will be easier than I thought
I mean this is my own house
So I just gotta feel my way around
Okay down the stairs
Get to the ground floor
Oh that's crap
I can't touch them either
Hell with it
I'll just jump out of the window
Oh lame
I hung them all over the yard yesterday
Because I was feeling all Christmasy
Fine man
I guess I'll retreat to the bathroom
And catch my breath
Oh one
Oh
Son of a
Something wrong?
I have the feeling Master is in danger
So?
Screw that guy
He needs to be taught a long overdue lesson
No way!
Those are adorable!
Oh look!
They have angel wings on them!
I bet they'd look perfect on you!
Wait a second!
I bet you're still wearing that same cheap ass pair of panties Tomoki bought for you at the convenience store right?
Look I'm sorry girl that's not gonna fly
You can't depend on that perverted mind of his
Good thing I'm here to help
I'll pick out some cute ones for you
Think of them as a present from me to you to thank you for the car
It's cute and it fits great!
So tell me a little about yourself
Is this the first time you've ever been someplace like this?
What do you do for fun?
Have you ever been shopping with your friends before?
With my friends?
I don't have friends
Oh I see
Icarus
I-I um
I'm sorry for asking such weird questions
I remember when I first moved here
I felt totally alone in the world
So I really do understand how you must feel
Back then my body was really weak and I had to stay indoors all the time
So uh Tomoki who lived next door
We became close friends
We were always there for each other
Sure he'd bring me worms and raid my family's fridge just like any typical boy
Sounds like him right?
But I remember one birthday
He was real sweet
Is something wrong sweetheart?
What are you standing out here for?
I thought when it was your birthday
A bunch of your friends were supposed to come over to your house for a party and have cake and ice cream
Today's my birthday
But no one came to my party
I'm all alone
Oh hey
Tomoki
This is real good
Hold on
That looks familiar
Is that the birthday cake my mom bought for me?
Happy birthday
And look Zohara
I got a present for you
My grandpa gave it to me yesterday
It's an orange tree seed
If you plant it
Your family will be able to eat oranges every year
Cool huh?
Do you like it?
Yeah
Sure brings back memories
He may act like an immature brat
But he's one of the few who understands just how other people feel
He's nice like that
It may come as a surprise but you can really count on him when it truly matters
But don't get me wrong 99% of the time he's just a creep
He probably won't say anything to you about it
But I'm pretty sure he cares about you too
And you know you do have friends
Just know you're not alone Icarus
Okay
Master is in serious danger
Hm
Alright
I'm starting to get worried myself
Let's head back to the house
Screw it
Make a run for the door and hope for the best
Hm
No!
What happened?
Are you okay?
Pull yourself together, Tomoki.
What are you doing here?
Icarus informed us of what happened.
We came to check up on the status of the panty situation.
I never would have expected this.
Looks like you've been through hell.
I guess...
I finally made it out of the house.
Hell yeah!
Hang on.
Where's Suhara?
She's inside of the house.
It looks as though the explosion caused her to be thrown back into the house.
That's crazy.
It's all my fault.
None of this would have happened if I hadn't landed face first in her crotch.
You know what to do, Tomoki.
You're the only one capable of saving Suhara from the danger that awaits her.
Ma'am.
Take this.
Whoa!
What the...
It's one of those times when a man stands up and fights.
Now get in there and bring an end to this deviant funhouse you've created.
That is, of course, if you're man enough for the job.
Oh, I am on this.
Sergeant Tomoki, ready for battle.
Wait for me, Suhara!
Master.
Now, you do realize you could send anyone other than Tomoki in there and the panties would never explode.
Oh, yes, Sagata.
I'm well aware of that fact.
But you have to admit, it's a lot more fun doing it this way, isn't it?
You're still as awful as you've ever been.
Suhara!
Where are you?
Don't you dare come near me!
Why are you running away?
My underwear exploded, thanks to you!
I've got freaking commando and it's your fault!
What was that?
Speak up!
I just want this to end!
Wait, Suhara!
Stay where you are!
Oh, crap.
Not my room.
Suhara!
Whatever you do, don't open the closet!
All my, uh, research materials...
Oh.
Wow, there's...
so much.
Quick!
Take cover!
I set up a booby trap in here to protect my treasure from outsiders!
The light!
What is that?
It's the booby trap I was trying to warn you about!
I was up all last night building it!
The Hyperfusion Panty Robot!
I have no choice!
The only way to save Suhara is to fight the Panty Robot!
But if any more panties explode right now, Suhara will be in deep trouble!
What should I do?
Suhara!
I have no choice!
The only way to save Suhara is to fight the Panty Robot!
But if any more panties explode right now, Suhara will be in deep trouble!
What should I do?
Suhara!
That voice!
Grandpa!
Suhara!
What's the matter, Grandpa?
You look hurt!
I ran into some trouble with the old lady, if you know what I mean.
Grandpa!
Listen up now, boy.
I never forget what your grandpa's about to tell you.
As a man like me, someday down the road you'll find something you like so much you won't
be able to give it up.
Odds are, it'll come back to haunt you in the end.
What will you do when that happens?
Will you turn tail and run?
Of course you won't.
Thank you, Grandpa.
As always, you've helped show me the light.
No, Lucky!
Save me!
That's it, Sonny Boy!
Grab what you'll love and hold on to it!
Yahoo!
I believe in you!
Ha!
Yah!
Show him, boy!
Yeah!
Show him what tomato!
What an anties!
Come to me!
Yes!
Yes, sir!
Yes.
Are they dead?
I'd say it's a definite possibility.
It is Master.
The battle is won, but not the war.
You're awake.
Oh, hey there.
Thank you, Tomo.
You saved my life, didn't you?
Listen, today was all my fault.
I'm sorry.
I'm laughing, I'm going to die
I'm going to die
Ah, open your eyes
Ah, you're a beautiful person
I'm looking for you
I can't see you
I'm not going to die
Pantser break!
Okay now, listen up
Your job is to protect my collection of booby mags at all costs
You are not to let anyone find them, you got me?
Whoa!
Well, I'm going to hit the sack
Had I known this would happen, I never would have sent an angel to you
I'm sorry
It looks like even you will get caught up in this mess
She's been spotted
I'm not going anywhere
Maybe we'll be sen USB
This is Twitter
That would be my computer
It's like we could still have yourlerde
I wonder if you would lay a laser
Next time, hot night with the big fish.